[{"question": "  hey everybody! happy thanksgiving!", "answer": " no, no, no. no-no-no. joey, rachel, and phoebe: shhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " what, are we keeping thanksgiving a secret this year?", "answer": " no, we're playing this game i learned at work. you have to name all the states in six minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what? that's like insanely easy!", "answer": " now, that's a lot harder than it sounds. you always forget at least one, or in some cases... fourteen .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " it's a stupid game and i wasn't playing against other people, so technically i didn't lose.", "answer": " what? you forgot fourteen states?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh, okay, time's up!", "answer": " all right, i got 48.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh that's not bad, pheebs?", "answer": " oh, i got tired of naming states. so i decided to list the types of celery, and i have one: regular celery.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " okay, so rachel's got 48 and phoebe has the lead in&#133;vegetables, joey?", "answer": " say hello to the new champ of chandler's dumb states game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " wow, how many have you got?", "answer": " fifty-six!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey! how is new england not a state? huh? they have a sports-team!", "answer": " does south oregon have a sports-team?  there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  how come we have one extra place setting?", "answer": " 'cause you invited your assistant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh, right. sorry. but tag's not coming; his girlfriend came into town, so he's spending thanksgiving with her.", "answer": " oh! why didn't you tell me? i made him his own individual sweet potato stuffed pumpkin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, i was going to, but then i figured, you know... you're food is so delicious and perfect, you can never have too many of those pumpkin things.", "answer": " now you think i wouldn't enjoy that, because it is so fake,  but i still do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " done! with time a-to-spare.", "answer": " oooh that may be a new world's record", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " you know, i hate to lecture you guys, but it's kinda disgraceful, that a group of well-educated adults and joey can't name all the states. did you ever see a map, or one of those round, colorful things called &quot;a globe?&quot; hmm?", "answer": " uh, magellan? you got 46 states.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what? that's impossible.", "answer": " 46. wow! who's well educated now, mr. i-forgot-ten-states?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " all right, i'm out of oven space. i'm gonna turn on joey's. please, watch him! do not let joey eat any of the food!", "answer": " i am only one man!  okay ross, time is up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " no, just give me another minute.", "answer": " look ross, if you don't know them by now, you will never know them, okay? that is the beauty of this game. it makes you want to kill yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " this-this is crazy! i can do this! all right, uhh, i bet i can get all 50 before dinner.", "answer": " okay, but if you can't&#133;no dinner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " you're on!", "answer": "  all right. don't look at my list, ross, 'cause there's a lot on there that you don't have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey, did you guys know, that your oven doesn't work?", "answer": " but the drawer full of take-out menus is okay, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " ross, i'm gonna use yours, okay?", "answer": " pshhshhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " sure, and joey; do not let ross look at any of the maps or the globe in your apartment.", "answer": " don't worry, chandler, it's not a globe of the united states.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hey you guys i'm gonna go out and take a walk.", "answer": " phoebe, why is your bag moving?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh, it's not!", "answer": " seriously, it's moving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " what the hell is in there?", "answer": " it's just my knitting that's all!  yes! i knit this. i'm very good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " ross&#146;s apartment is nice! how come we don't hang out here more often?", "answer": " i don't know. maybe it's because it smells a little weird. it's like old pumpkins or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " that's my pie!", "answer": " which smells delicious!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " uh-oh! uh-oh!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  hi geller-bing residence. how can i help?", "answer": " phoebe, why is there a dog in our apartment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i'm sorry, who's this?", "answer": " phoebe, there's a dog sitting on my couch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " tell her, i'm allergic, and i will sue!", "answer": " no, there's no dog here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yes there is! he's black and white and shaggy and  he's sitting next to rachel and licking rachel's hand.", "answer": " oh my god! where are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i'll be right there!", "answer": "  they're here already? how are they doing this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hi tag! what are you doing here?", "answer": " i, uh, wanted to see if your offer to spend thanksgiving with you is still good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " well, sure! come in!  well, what-what happened to your girlfriend?", "answer": " we kinda broke up this morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, i'm sorry.", "answer": " yeah, so she went back to ohio.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " huh! where is the dog?!", "answer": " what dog? there-there's no dog here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yeah that dog left!", "answer": "  phoebe! phoebe, open up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " phoebe, we can hear the dog barking!", "answer": " no that's just me coughing!  oh, good, there you are! listen, um, i have a dog in my room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " what is it doing here?", "answer": " well, i'm watching it for some friends who went out of town. wait.  hello, my name is clunkers. may i please stay with you nice people?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oooh, i wish she could stay here, but chandler is allergic!", "answer": " extremely allergic, okay? if i'm anywhere near a dog for more than 5 minutes, my throat will just close up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " that's odd, 'cause this dog's been living here for the past 3 days", "answer": "  really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " chandler, if that dog's been here that long, and you haven't had a reaction, maybe you're not allergic to this dog?", "answer": " well, it still has to go, right? monica and phoebe: why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " okay, it's um&#133;", "answer": "  don't do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " don't do what?", "answer": "  i have to! okay? it's time!  okay, i hate dogs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " are you crazy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " are you out of your mind?", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " they are needy, they are jumpy, and you can't tell what they are thinking, and that scares me a little bit.", "answer": " right, they are scary.  ahh, she just ate a treat out of my hand!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " wait a minute. do you not like all dogs? i mean, not even puppies?", "answer": "  is there a puppy here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " you don't like puppies?", "answer": "  okay, you are new!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " look, chandler, i told you, never tell anyone about this dog thing. it's like ross not likin&#146; ice cream.", "answer": " you don't like ice cream?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " it's too cold.", "answer": " okay, it's just that dogs make me a little uncomfortable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  it hurts my teeth.", "answer": " and i don't wanna say this, i don't you guys to hate me, but uh, i don't think, i can be around that dog anymore. okay, so either the dog goes, or i go.  oh my god!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " how can i not get this? i'm a college professor; i got 1450 on my s.a.t.s.", "answer": " 1250.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " damn, i forgot you were here.", "answer": " all right. we're gonna take clunkers to ross&#146;s. we'll be back in a minute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh, wait before you guys go, can i just ask you a question?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " when a guy breaks up with his girlfriend, what is an appropriate amount of time to wait before you make a move?", "answer": " oh, i'd say about a month.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " really? i'd say 3 to 4.", "answer": " half hour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " interesting.", "answer": " when it's your assistant, i would say never.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " all right, rach, the big question is, does he like you? all right? because if he doesn't like you, this is all a moo-point.", "answer": " huh. a moo-point?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yeah, it's like a cow's opinion. it just doesn't matter. it's moo.", "answer": "  have i been living with him for too long, or did that all just make sense?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " please, don't listen to joey, okay. would you look at him? he-he&#146;s obviously depressed. he's away from his family; he's spending thanksgiving with strangers. what he needs right now is for you to be his friend.", "answer": " you're right, i'm sorry. thank you. okay, that's what i'm gonna do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " how are you holding up?", "answer": " not bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yeah? i'm sorry about your girlfriend.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " so were you guys together a long time?", "answer": " a year. on and off. i kinda thought we'd end up together. i don't anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " now that she broke up with you?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah. hmmmm.", "answer": " it's weird. i always used to assume, that i would meet someone and fall in love and be happy and all that was just a given. but lately it's like what if it's not. do you ever have that feeling?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " no&#133;yeah, all the time, constantly. it's terrifying. but you know that i figure it&#133;it has to work out.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " because, uh&#151;it has to.", "answer": " you have all the answers, don't you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah, i know, i do. i really do.", "answer": " hey, thanks for talking to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  all right, he likes you back! huh? told ya, you should go for it!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " what did joey say? i like you back?", "answer": " uh, yeah, well, see, he&#133; joey knows, that i'm-i'm very insecure about my back and, and&#133;you're hugging me, so obviously you are not repulsed by it, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " wait-wait a minute; that doesn't make any sense.", "answer": " no?  all right, here's the truth um, joey said what he said, because um, i'm attracted to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yeah, i admit it. i have a crush on you, and uh, and, and i know that's crazy because we work together, and-and nothing could ever happen, and the last thing i want to do is-is to freak you out or make you feel uncomfortable. which is why it would be really great if you said something right about now.", "answer": "  oh my god! those guys are stealing my car!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " right there! that's my car!  hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " okay, that's gonna take them a minute. do you have anything else you wanna get off your chest?", "answer": " i can't believe this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " okay phoebe, we should probably go back now.", "answer": "  please don't leave me, i'll be lonely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " stop it. stop! okay let's go. we can be strong.", "answer": " yeah, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " oh my god! did you hear that? she said monica!  oooh, i can't leave her!", "answer": " you know if you want, we can sneak the dog back in and chandler wouldn't even know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " that's not gonna work.", "answer": " i've had that dog there for three days and chandler had no idea. he's not so smart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey! i didn't know either.", "answer": " yeah, but you kinda knew that something was going on, didn't you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " where's chandler?", "answer": "  here i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " wash your hands!!!", "answer": " how did you&#133;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hey! what's she doing back here?", "answer": " relax, ross. she's not made of ice cream!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " hey look, phoebe. i, uh, i laid out the states geographically...", "answer": "  no, no, we don't really have time for this right now. okay, we have to keep chandler away from my bedroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " yeah, but, but look what i'm...", "answer": " see, this is exactly what we do not have time for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  where's monica?", "answer": " um, in phoebe's room. you can't go in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " monica's crying. she's very upset about this whole clunkers thing.", "answer": " well, i, i should go in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " no. no, no. she doesn't want to see you right now.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " because you sent away the dog!", "answer": " this is ridiculous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh, is it? is it? look, when monica and i were kids, we had a dog named rover. and, uh, one day, my dad decides, he doesn't like dogs. so monica and her friend&#133;phyllis&#133;take away the dog. and that was the last time we ever saw him. don't you see? this is just like that. only with a few details changed.", "answer": "  okay, i'm in my sweat pants. bring on the food!  what's the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " monica's all upset, because i sent clunkers away.", "answer": " so? bring the dog back, you're a hero.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " yeah, i can be a hero, i could do that. i could, i could do... i, w-w-what if, what if it attacks me?", "answer": " chandler, it's like a big gerbil.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ross, you need some help?", "answer": " from you?  yes, please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " hey! tag's still talking to the police.", "answer": " yeah, ohh! why, damnit, why did i open my mouth?  i have a crush on you; i am attracted to you.  gee, i-i know that i freaked him out", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  hey, is chandler here?", "answer": " no, no he went for a walk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " oh no-no-no-no-no-no-no! he went over to ross' to bring the dog back here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " oh no, the dog's not going to be there!", "answer": " you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hi, honey.", "answer": " please, please, please, don't be mad at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what? why, why would...", "answer": "  shh, wait and see. maybe we will, maybe we won't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " we have good news, look whose back!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " clunkers?! oh my god!", "answer": " that's right, she came back all by herself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " it's a thanksgiving miracle!", "answer": "  it is so good to see you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " okay, maybe this is so hard, because there aren't 50 states. let me tell you something, i have 49 states, and there are no more! i-i think, i should be able to eat something.", "answer": " it's up to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh, hi! how are you doing?", "answer": " i'm okay. i gotta go down to the police station and look at mug shots.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " thanks for having me over, you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " tag? y-you're going?  uh we didn't, uh we didn't get the chance to talk. uh, so, where did you say you're from again?", "answer": " colorado.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " look, um, i think we should talk about what happened on the terrace.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " ah, i-i never should have said what i said. it&#151;y&#146;know what? it just doesn't matter how i feel. i mean we work together, so nothing could really ever happen between us, and what i would love is just to go to work on monday, and-and never talk about this again, okay? big day monday lots to do. so, we're okay?", "answer": " um, i'm not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh, god, i know it, that i freaked you out.", "answer": " no, you didn't. the only thing that freaked me out was you saying that nothing could ever happen between us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah, so, please don't fire me for doing this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " delaware!  delaware!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": "  i want my turkey now!", "answer": " you got it.  you got nevada twice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  i know.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}]